Opening Theme Song
Look carefully with your heart
Discover the truth is right before your eyes
Hey you could or better, true and false
No escape from this soul's grey smoke
Bring all your courage
Maybe then you'll save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
Fallen Angel
Locky, why is this?!
Why do Locky and Jingjing get to skip school every day?
Yeah!
How did we just notice this?!
Easy, son.
Don't ask questions like that anymore.
Mommy will take you to McDonnie's later.
Do all the main characters in your junk cartoons skip school?!
Sorry
Heh heh, that's how you write it.
Why is it in cartoons
Locky and Jingjing can skip school every day?
Sorry
I want this one, okay?
Why is it that in cartoons
Locky and Jingjing don't have to go to school every day?!
Oh, sorry, sorry!
This is the hardest part.
I'm doomed!
Doing homework till midnight every day
Woken up by you at the crack of dawn
Poor kids who have to go to school.
[Did you forget your schoolbag?]
I actually did forget my schoolbag!
It hurts so much!
What's going on?
Poor me.
It's been ages since I've had any customers.
Could it be that people in this town don't like ice cream anymore?
Oh heavens!
I beg you, send me a customer!
This must be the customer heaven has sent me!
Little girl, little girl!
I have chocolate, vanilla, blueberry, cola ice cream
All kinds of flavors!
Ice cream!
I'll sell them all to you!
All to you!
Don't run!
There's also taro flavor.
There's also taro flavor...
Taro flavor....
My savior!
So unlike.
Being alone isn't just loneliness.
The me at that time.
Mingjing needs your support. Subscribe to Mingjing.
You, the late king!
Come to the office with me.